Guide to the Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 1
Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 1
- Box: 12, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Die Scheinfirma: Moderne Berufsausbildung, 1957; Publication (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Draft for the Resolution of the 5th CongressGerman Trade Unions, 1959; Publication (Box 12, Folder 2)
    Author: Confederation of Free German Trade Unions
    Notes: draft
  - Item 9: Material on the Situation in West Berlin, 1960; Publication (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Proposals for a Competition between the FDGB and the DGB, Publication (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: Proposals for a Competition between the FDGB and the DGB, Publication (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: Rechnungsabschlub und Statistische Ubersichten, 1958; Publication (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: Vorlesungs-Verzeichnis, 1959; Publication (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Item 14: 10 Years of Childrens' Happy Laughter, 1960; Publication (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Item 15: 10 Years of Childrens' Happy Laughter, 1960; Publication (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Item 16: Democratic German Report, 1956; Publication (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Item 17: International Forum of the Confederation of Free German Trade Unions, 1960; Publication (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Item 18: International Forum of the Confederation of Free German Trade Unions, 1960; Publication (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Item 19: Tatsachen uber Deutschland, 1957; Publication (Box 12, Folder 2)
    Author: Helmut Arntz
- Box: 12, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Om Broederschap en Harmonie, 1978; Publication (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Lecture on Trade UnionsGermany - 16 March 1976, Publication (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Collective Agreement for the Social Protection.District of Hanover, 1987; Publication (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Master Contract for Hourly Rated EmployeesDistrict of Hanover, 1965; Publication (Box 12, Folder 3)
    Author: Volkswagen Works, Inc.
  - Item 5: Master Contract for Hourly Rated EmployeesDistrict of Hanover, 1964; Publication (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Social Reports of the German Federal Republic, 1970-71, 1972; Publication (Box 12, Folder 3)
    Notes: article; reprint from the Social Security Bulletin, July 1972
  - Item 7: Settlement of Social Conflicts in the Federal Republic of Germany, 1972; Publication (Box 12, Folder 3)
    Author: Heinz Ruhnau
  - Item 8: German Policy for Peace and Security in Europe, 1972; Publication (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: New Frontiers on the Rhine, 1963; Publication (Box 12, Folder 3)
    Author: Kenneth Ames
  - Item 10: The Quarterly Journal of Economics (Prosperity and Labor Relations in Europe: The Case of West Germany), 1962; Publication (Box 12, Folder 3)
    Notes: serial - photocopy
- Box: 12, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Labor in the Federal Republic of Germany, 1958; Publication (Box 12, Folder 4)
    Author: U.S. Dept. of Labor
  - Item 2: Veroffentlichungen des Deutschen Industreinstituts 1951-1961, Publication (Box 12, Folder 4)
    Author: Deutsches Industrieinstitut
- Box: 12, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Labor Relations in Postwar Germany, 1957; Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Look at the Record: The ManifestoGerman Demokratic Republic, 1962; Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
    Author: Gretel Bischoff
  - Item 3: Look at the Record: The ManifestoGerman Demokratic Republic, 1962; Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Trade Union Enemies in Judges Robes: AWest Germany Today, 1962; Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Trade Union Enemies in Judges Robes: AWest Germany Today, 1962; Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Who Split Germany?: Wall Street and the West German Trade Unions, 1962; Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
    Author: George Shaw Wheeler
- Box: 12, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Our Objectives, 1963; Publication (Box 12, Folder 6)
    Author: Georg Leber
  - Item 2: Collective bargaining and the law governing collective agreements, 1963; Publication (Box 12, Folder 6)
    Author: Hans Reichel
  - Item 3: Satzung der Industriegewerkschaft Druck und Papier, 1965; Publication (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Satzung der Industriegewerkschaft Metall fur dieDeutschland, 1969; Publication (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Archiv fur Sozial geschichte, Publication (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: 2. Mai 1993 Tatsachen und Lehren, 1963; Publication (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Actual Aims and Problems of German Trade Unions, 1969; Publication (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: Executive Employees and the DGB, 1975; Publication (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: Non-Manual Workers and the DGB, 1975; Publication (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Item 10: La Politique Sociale en Allemagne: Les travailleursd'Allemagne, 1965; Publication (Box 12, Folder 6)
    Author: Politique Sociale en Allemagne
  - Item 11: Le droit de cogestion des travailleurs dans laAllemande, 1964; Publication (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Item 12: Old Age and Sickness Insurance in West Germany in 1965, Publication (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Box: 12, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Basic Programme of the German Trade Union Federation, 1963; Publication (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Der Schweizerische GewerkschaftsbundBildungswesens, 1967; Publication (Box 12, Folder 7)
    Author: Rolf Kramer
  - Item 3: Die christlichen GewerkschaftenGrundsatzprogramm des DGB, 1963; Publication (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Akademie der Arbeit in der Universitat Frankfurt am Main, Publication (Box 12, Folder 7)
    Author: Akademie der Arbeit (Frankfurt am Main, Germany)
  - Item 5: Our Objectives, 1963; Publication (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: Our Objectives, 1963; Publication (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: The Workers and their Social Insurance System, 1966; Publication (Box 12, Folder 7)
    Author: Gunther Thude
- Box: 12, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Etude du Marche de l'Emploi et du Chomage Secouru, 1957; Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Evolution du Marche du Travail: France Entiere, 1956; Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Ghana aluminum products limited wages and salaries appendix, 1964; Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
    Author: Ghana Aluminum Products Limited
    Notes: not found on list
  - Item 4: Monthly Figures of Lay-Offs and Placements, July 1966 to April 1967, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Monthly Figures of Lay-Offs and Placements, July 1966 to May 1967, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: Collective Agreement, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
    Notes: pretty generic agreement, not enough info to catalog
  - Item 7: Accra Employment Market Report for the Quarter Ended 30th September, 1963, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
    Author: Employment Information Branch, Labour Dept., Accra
  - Item 8: Accra Employment Market Report for the Quarter Ended 31st March 1963, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Item 9: Accra Employment Market Report for the Quarter Ended 30th June, 1964, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Item 10: Accra Employment Market Report for the Quarter Ended 31st March, 1964, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Item 11: Accra Employment Market Report for the Quarter 31st December, 1963, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Item 12: Agreement between Bank of West Arica Ltd./Barclays Bank D.C.O. and the Industrial, Commercial and General Workers' Union of the Trades Union Congress (Ghana), 1964; Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Item 13: Agreement between the Industrial, Commercial and Catering Trades Union of T.U.C. (Ghana) and Ghana Household Utilities Mfg. Co. Limited, 1966; Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Item 14: Agreement between the Pioneer Tobacco Company Limited (Incorporation in Ghana) and the Industrial and Commercial Workers Union, 1967; Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Item 15: Greater Accra Employment Market Report for the Quarter ended 30th September, 1964, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Item 16: Kumasi Employment Market Report for the Quarter ended 30th June, 1964, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Item 17: Kumasi Employment Market Report for the Quarter ended 30th June, 1963, Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Box: 12, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Ghana: Anatomy of a Change, 1965; Publication (Box 12, Folder 9)
    Author: J. Kirk Sale
  - Item 2: The Labor Movement of Ghana: A Study in Political Unionism, 1962; Publication (Box 12, Folder 9)
    Notes: reprined for private circulation from the Economic Development and Cultural Change
  - Item 3: Dear Editor (Wallerstein), 1966; Publication (Box 12, Folder 9)
    Author: Immanuel Wallerstein
  - Item 4: New T.U.C. Structure - Your National Unions, 1960; Publication (Box 12, Folder 9)
    Notes: company structure outline
  - Item 5: Trade Unions in Chains, 1966; Publication (Box 12, Folder 9)
    Author: B.A. Bentum
  - Item 6: A New Chpater for Ghana Labour, 1958; Publication (Box 12, Folder 9)
    Author: John K. Tettegah
  - Item 7: Salaries and Conditions of Service for State Enterprises, 1966; Publication (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: Nkrumah Steps Up Nkrumahism: To achieveEastern bloc, 1962; Publication (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Item 9: Portrait of Nkrumah as Dictator: In Ghana todayagainst the state, 1964; Publication (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Box: 12, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Service Conditions Agreement between Industrial, Commercial and General Workers Union of the Trades Union Congress (Ghana) and the Insurance Companies (collective bargaining certificate of 5th June 1961), Publication (Box 12, Folder 10)
    Notes: couldn't find on sheet
  - Item 2: Service Conditions Agreement between Industrial, Commercial and Catering Trades Union of T.U.C. (Ghana) and Harmood-Banner, Midgley, Snelling, Barnes & Co., 1966; Publication (Box 12, Folder 10)
    Notes: brief
  - Item 3: AgreementBetween the Industrial, Commercial and General Workers Union of T.U.C. (Ghana) [and] Aluminium Factory Limited, 1963; Publication (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: Salaries and Wages Agreement betweenGhamaco Limited, 1965; Publication (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: Kumasi Employment Market Report for the QuarterJune, 1963, Publication (Box 12, Folder 10)
    Author: Labour Dept., Accra
    Notes: quarterly
  - Item 6: Accra Employment Market Report for the Quarter Ended1963, Publication (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: Accra Employment Market Report for the QuarterDecember, 1962, Publication (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Item 8: Agreement Between the Industrial, Commercial and Catering Trades Union of T.U.C. and the Commercial Employers, 1966; Publication (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Item 9: AgreementBetween Ghana Cargo Handling Company Limited and the Maritime and Dockworkers' Union of T.U.C., 1967; Publication (Box 12, Folder 10)
    Notes: brief not really something to catalog
  - Item 10: AgreementBetween Ghana Cargo Handling Limited... And the Maritime and Dockworkers' Union of T.U.C., 1967; Publication (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Item 11: AgreementBetween the Ghana Port Employers' Assoc. .. And the Maritime & Dockworkers Union of T.U.C., The Employer representing shipping Companies/Agencies in Ghana and the Union representing Employees employed by the Members of the Association, 1967; Publication (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Item 12: Agreement between the Industrial, Commercialand Terco Ltd., 1963; Publication (Box 12, Folder 10)
    Author: Industrial, Commercial and General Workers' Union of the Trades Union Congress; Terco Ltd.
  - Item 13: Agreement between the Industrial, Commercialand L'Air Liquide, 1964; Publication (Box 12, Folder 10)
    Author: Industrial, Commercial and General Workers' Union of the Trades Union Congress; L'Air liquide (Firm)
  - Item 14: Agreement between Shell Ghana LimitedUnion of the T.U.C., 1966; Publication (Box 12, Folder 10)
    Author: Shell Ghana Limited; General Transport and Petroleum Workers Union
  - Item 15: Agreement between the IndustrialRose & Company Limited, 1965; Publication (Box 12, Folder 10)
    Author: Industrial, Commercial and Catering Trades Union; L. Rose and Company Ltd.
  - Item 16: Collective Agreement between the Construction & General Workers' Union of T.U.C.(Ghana) Ltd., the National Contractors' Assoc. and the Civil Engineers & Builders' Federation of Ghana Limited, Publication (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Item 17: Agreement of Minimum Rates of Pay and conditions of service between the Planters Assoc. of Ghana...1st of July, 1962, Publication (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Item 18: Agreement between the I.C.U. and Lever Brothers Ghana Limited, 1964; Publication (Box 12, Folder 10)
    Author: Industrial, Commercial and General Workers' Union of the Trades Union Congress; Lever Brothers Ghana Ltd.
  - Item 19: Agreement between Glamour Garment Factory Limited and Industrial, Commercial & General Workers' Union of the T.U.C., 1962; Publication (Box 12, Folder 10)
    Author: Industrial, Commercial and General Workers' Union of the Trades Union Congress; Glamour Garment Factory Ltd.
  - Item 20: Ghana Timber Federation: National Agreement on minimum rates of pay and conditions of service for employees in the Timber Trade, 1964; Publication (Box 12, Folder 10)
    Author: Ghana Timber Federation
  - Item 21: Agreement between the I.C.U. and Dorman Long Limited, 1963; Publication (Box 12, Folder 10)
    Author: Industrial, Commercial and General Workers' Union of the Trades Union Congress; Dorman Long Ltd.
  - Item 22: Agreed Service Conditions for the employees of the Kumasi Brewery LimitedUnion of Catering Trades of the Trades Union Congress (Ghana) ...the Employer, 1964; Publication (Box 12, Folder 10)
    Author: Kumasi Brewery Ltd.; Union of Catering Trades of the Trades Union Congress
  - Item 23: Agreement between Mobil Oil Ghana Limited and the Mobil Oil Division of the Posts, Transport and Maritime Workers' Union of the T.U.C. (Ghana), 1966; Publication (Box 12, Folder 10)
    Author: Mobil Oil Ghana Ltd.; Posts, Transport and Maritime Workers' Union of the Trades Union Congress
  - Item 24: Agreement between the Ghana Manufacturers' Group and the Industrial, Commercial and General Workers' Union and the Union of Catering Trades (TUC), 1964; Publication (Box 12, Folder 10)
    Author: Ghana Manufacturers' Group; Industrial, Commercial and General Workers' Union of the Trades Union Congress; Union of Catering Trades of the Trades Union Congress
- Box: 12, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: The Gold Coast Trades Union Congress Policy Statement, 1954; Publication (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Box: 13, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: A Social and Economic History of Britain 1760-1950, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: A Social and Economic History of Britain 1760-1950, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
    Author: Pauline Gregg
  - Item 3: Industry and democracy: the problem of workers' control, an historical outline., 1952; Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
    Author: Maurice B. Reckitt
  - Item 4: Training Manual for Branch Officers, 1975; Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
    Author: Transport and General Workers' Union (Great Britain)
- Box: 13, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Report of the Seventeenth Annual GeneralJuly 5th, 6th and 7th, 1916, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Agenda for the 51st Annual CongressGlasgow, Monday1919, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Trade Unionism, A General Survey in 12 Lessons: HistoryPolicy, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
    Author: Trades Unions Congress
  - Item 4: Report of the Annual Public MeetingLondon, May 21st, 1914, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
    Author: Labour Co-partnership Association (Great Britain)
  - Item 5: Labour and Leisure: Some Proposals Drawn UpLabour Colleges, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
    Author: National Council of Labour Colleges (Great Britain)
  - Item 6: Whitley Councils: What They Are and What They Are Doing, 1920; Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
    Author: J.H. Whitley
  - Item 7: The Aims of Labour, 1918; Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
    Author: Arthur Henderson
  - Item 8: The Story of the Trades Union Congress, 1925; Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
    Author: Fred Bramley
  - Item 9: Education of Cooperators, 1882; Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
    Author: Arnold Toynbee
  - Item 10: Relations between Employers and Employed - after the War, 1918; Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
    Author: Hubert B. Graham
  - Item 11: Architects' Benevolent Society, 1901; Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
    Author: Architects Benevolent Society
  - Item 12: Bias in the Schools, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
    Author: J.P.M. Millar
- Box: 13, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Report on Unemployment, 1910; Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
    Author: Christian Social Union (Great Britain)
  - Item 2: Infant Mortality, 1905; Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
    Author: Margaret McMillan
  - Item 3: Co-Partnership in Practice, 1914; Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
    Author: Henry Harvey Vivian
  - Item 4: The Guild Idea: An Appeal to the Public, 1915; Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
    Author: National Guilds League (Great Britain)
  - Item 5: What is Imperialism?, 1944; Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
    Author: T. Aschcroft
  - Item 6: Report of the Proceedings of the Inaugural Meeting1918, Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
    Author: Industrial Council for the Building Industry
    Notes: article reprinted from "The Builder"
  - Item 7: Women and Children in the Textile Industry: An InternationalEntry, 1922; Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
    Author: Marion Phillips
  - Item 8: Compromise or Independence?: An ExaminationIndustrial Councils, 1918; Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
    Author: J.T. Murphy
  - Item 9: The War Traders: An Exposure, 1913; Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
    Author: George Herbert Perris
  - Item 10: Workers' Control in Industry, 1919; Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
    Author: G.D.H. Cole
  - Item 11: Trade Unionism: A New Model, 1919; Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
    Author: Robert Page Arnot
  - Item 12: Industrial Unionism, 1919; Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
    Author: Building Workers' Industrial Union (Great Britain)
  - Item 13: Industrial Unionism: What it is and What it isn't, 1917; Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
    Author: E.L. Pratt
  - Item 14: Capital and Labour: A SeriesPermanent Removal of Labour Unrest, 1918; Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
    Author: Charles W. Macara
  - Item 15: Protective Clothing for Women and Girl Workersand Workshops, 1917; Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
    Author: Great Britain. Home Office
  - Item 16: National Guilds or Whitley Councils?, 1918; Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Item 17: Towards a National Railway Guild, 1917; Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Item 18: A Catechism of National Guilds, 1918; Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Item 19: The Industrial Chaos: The Labour Crisis and theNational Guilds, Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Item 20: Constitution and Rules (adopted 1st August, 1918), Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Item 21: National Guilds: An Appeal to Trade Unionists, Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
    Author: National Guilds League, London
  - Item 22: Sixty Years of Trade Unionism: Interview with Mr. Robert Applegarth, 1916; Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
    Notes: article reprinted from "The Christian Commonwealth"
  - Item 23: Co-Partnership Organisation of Labour, 1914; Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
    Author: E.W. Bundy
  - Item 24: Thirty-First Annual Report for the year ended December 31st, 1916, Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Box: 13, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Second interim report of the committee appointed to enquire into the organisation and staffing of government offices, 1918; Publication (Box 13, Folder 4)
    Author: Great Britain. Committee on Staffs
  - Item 2: Third interim report of the committee appointed to enquire into the organisation and staffing of government offices, 1918; Publication (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Fourth interim report of the committee appointed to enquire into the organisation and staffing of government offices, 1918; Publication (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Final report of the committee appointed to enquire into the organisation and staffing of government offices, 1918; Publication (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Final report / Great Britain. Ministry of Reconstruction. Committee on Relations Between Employers and Employed, 1915; Publication (Box 13, Folder 4)
    Author: Great Britain. Ministry of Reconstruction. Committee on Relations Between Employers and Employed
  - Item 6: Havelock Wilson's Confession and warning to dockers, Publication (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Committee on Relations between Employers & Employed: Final Report, 1918; Publication (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Committee on...Employers & Employed: Second ReportCouncils, 1918; Publication (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Thirtieth Report 1915, Publication (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Interim report of the committee appointed to enquire into the organisation and staffing of government offices, 1918; Publication (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Supplementary report on works committees, 1918; Publication (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: Co-Partnership after the War, 1917; Publication (Box 13, Folder 4)
    Author: Labour Co- partnership Association (Great Britain)
  - Item 13: Health of Munition Workers Committee: Memorandum No. 19Dietary, 1917; Publication (Box 13, Folder 4)
    Author: Great Britain. Ministry of Munitions. Health of Munition Workers Committee
  - Item 14: Health of Munition Workers Committee: Memorandum No. 19Dietary, 1917; Publication (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Item 15: Washing facilities and baths ..., 1916; Publication (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Item 16: Health of Munition Workers Committee: Memorandumas to Dietary, 1916; Publication (Box 13, Folder 4)
    Author: Leonard Hill
  - Item 17: Health of Munition Workers Committee: Memorandumas to Dietary, 1916; Publication (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Item 18: Health of Munition Workers Committee: MemorandumWeekly hours of Employment, 1917; Publication (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Item 19: Health of Munition Workers Committee: MemorandumWeekly hours of Employment, 1917; Publication (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Item 20: Health of Munition Workers Committee: MemorandumSunday Labour, 1915; Publication (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Item 21: Health of Munition Workers Committee: MemorandumSunday Labour, 1915; Publication (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Item 22: Labor War Aims, 1918; Publication (Box 13, Folder 4)
    Author: Inter-Allied Labour and Socialist Conference
- Box: 13, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Statutory Rules and Orders, 1926, No. 451, Emergency, Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Official Report: Parliamentary Debates, House of Commons, 1926; Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: The Organisation of Women In Trade Unions Great Britain, 1923; Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
    Author: Women's Dept., Trades Union Congress General Council
  - Item 4: Works Rules made with the approval of the Central Works Council, 1921; Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
    Author: Rowntree & Company Ltd.
  - Item 5: The Meaning of the General Strike, 1926; Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
    Author: R. Plame Dutt
  - Item 6: Why Socialism Must Come, 1924; Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
    Author: James Ramsay MacDonald
  - Item 7: The Labour College, 1922; Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
    Notes: curriculum catalog
  - Item 8: J. Havelock Wilson's Attempt to Enslave British Seamen Exposed, 1922; Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
    Author: J. Havelock Wilson
  - Item 9: Labour and the Nation, 1929; Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)